Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1927-2010 and undated, bulk 1956-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series (RESTRICTED), 1935-2004 and undated, (92 boxes)
  - Writings by Price Subseries (RESTRICTED), 1946-2003 and undated, (76 boxes)
    - A Common Room (essays, 1987) RESTRICTED (Box WP21)
      - The Penny Show, manuscript and galley proof, 1982 Dec. 14-15 and undated
      - Pictures of Pride, manuscripts and typescripts, 1976 Dec. and undated
      - Real Life and Fiction, notes, manuscript, and typescripts, 1982 and undated
      - A Recurrent Fact, draft, undated
      - Reviews
        - Blotner, Joseph, Faulkner: A Biography, manuscript and typescript, 1974 and undated
        - Greene, Graham, The Honorary Consul and Collected Stories, manuscript and typescript, 1973 and undated
        - Hemingway, Gregory, Papa: a Personal Memoir, manuscripts and typescripts, 1976 and undated
        - Lattimore, Richmond, Acts and Letters of the Apostles, typescript, undated
        - Lattimore, Richmond, The Four Gospels and the Revelation, manuscript and typescript, 1973 and undated
        - Morrison, Toni, Song of Solomon, manuscript, 1977
        - Welch, James, Winter in the Blood, manuscript and typescript, 1974 Oct. 9 and undated
      - A Start, manuscript, 1981 Sept. 28-Oct. 13
      - Strong Old Rhythms, manuscript and typescripts, 1979 Jan. 7 and undated
      - The Thing Itself, manuscripts and typescripts, 1966, 1971, and undated, (6 folders)
      - Uses for Freedoms, manuscript and typescripts, 1967-1971 and undated
      - A Vast Common Room, drafts and typescript, 1986
      - What Stayed in Plains, manuscript, 1980 Nov. 24
      - You Are Needed Now and Will Always Be, manuscripts and typescripts, 1975 Mar. 17-Oct. 8 and undated
      - Early typescripts, 1964-1985 and undated, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Early typescripts, 1964-1985 and undated, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WP22)
      - Early typescript, miscellaneous, undated
      - Printer's copy, with Harry Ford's specifications, 1987, (12 folders)
      - Galley proof, miscellaneous pages, 1987
      - First proof, with Harry Ford's and Price's corrections, 1987 Aug. 27
      - Master proof, miscellaneous pages with Price's corrections, 1987 Aug. 27
      - Jacket sketch, by Harry Ford, undated
      - Jacket, undated
    - Full Moon (play, 1987) RESTRICTED (Box WP23)
      - Typescript draft, 1987
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, undated
      - Typescript second draft with author's revisions, 1987 July-Oct., (2 folders)
      - Typescript second draft with author's revisions, 1987 Sept.-Oct.
      - Typescript fragments with revisions by author, undated
      - Bound copy, undated
      - Typescript of the premier production, 1988 Aug. 4
      - Full Moon and Other Plays, corrected proof, 1993, (2 folders)
    - Good Hearts (novel, 1988) RESTRICTED (Box WP24)
      - Typescript draft, 1986 Aug.
      - Typescript draft, 1988, (3 folders)
      - First proof with Price's and Harry Ford's changes, 1988, (2 folders)
      - Second proof with Price's changes, 1988, (2 folders)
      - Ad copy, undated
      - Publicity schedule, 1988
    - Clear Pictures (memoir, 1989) RESTRICTED (Box WP24)
      - Foreward, typescript drafts with corrections, 1988
      - Three Useful Lessons: typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1987 and undated
      - An Open Heart, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1987 and undated
      - Black Help, typescript drafts with author's corrections, undated (Box WP25)
      - An Absolute Hunter, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1987 and undated
      - A Normal, All But Fatal Childhood, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1988 and undated
      - Real Copies, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1987-1988 and undated
      - Credible Light, (Absolute Reality) typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1988 and undated, (Folder 1 of 3)
      - Credible Light, (Absolute Reality) typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1988 and undated, (Folders 2-3 of 3)
      - A Final Secret: Will's Death, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1988 and undated
      - Miscellaneous revised pages, undated
      - Afterword (Epilogue), typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1987-1989 and undated
      - Captions for illustrations, draft with author's corrections and notes on illustrations, 1988 and undated
      - A Note on Clear Pictures, typescript drafts with author's corrections, 1988
      - Typescript draft, 1988, (3 folders)
      - Binding die copy, 1989, (Folder 1 of 4)
      - Binding die copy, 1989, (Folders 2-4 of 4) (Box WP26)
      - Afterword, corrected proof, 1989 Mar.
      - Proofs and notes on illustrations, 1989, (3 folders)
      - Changes for a second printing, undated
      - Jacket copy, undated
      - Promotional folder and contents, 1989
    - The Tongues of Angels (novel, 1990) RESTRICTED (Box WP26)
      - Research notes, undated
      - Typescript first draft with author's revisions, undated
      - Typescript second draft with author's revisions, 1987 Sept.
      - Typescript third draft with author's revisions, 1987 Sept., (2 folders)
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, undated
      - Typescript draft, circa 1987
      - Printer's copy with specifications, undated, (2 folders)
      - Spelling notes for copy editor, 1989 June
      - Printer's proof, 1989 Nov.
      - Printer's first proof and master proof, 1990
      - Ultramarine Publishing Company Flyer, circa 1989 (Box WP27)
      - "First changes," manuscript notes, undated
      - Cover proofs, undated
    - The Use of Fire (poetry, 1990) RESTRICTED (Box WP27)
      - An Afterlife, 1953-1988, typescripts, 1989
      - An Afterlife, 1953-1958, galley proof, 1990
      - Dawn (John 21), typescripts, 1989
      - The Eel, typescripts, 1984
      - The Elephants of North Carolina (Also Dream Elephants), typescripts, 1989
      - Fishers, typescript, 1988
      - Giant, typescripts, 1990
      - Half of Life, manuscript and typescript, 1970 and undated
      - Hymn, manuscript and typescripts, 1989
      - Initiation, manuscript and typescript, 1970 and undated
      - Imprecation, typescript, undated
      - Jim, Dead of AIDS an Hour Ago, typescript, 1988
      - Jim, With AIDS, typescript, 1988
      - Juncture, typescripts, 1987
      - Late Visit, manuscripts, 1989
      - Lights Out, manuscripts, 1988
      - Lost Homes, typescripts, 1989, and undated
      - Maya, typescript, 1990
      - Noon Rest, Best Day, manuscript and limited edition, Albondocani Press, 1986, (2 folders)
      - The Resident Heron, typescript, 1988
      - Six Consolations, typescripts, 1989
      - Socrates and Alcibiades, manuscripts, typescripts, and proof, 1960-1980 and undated
      - Three Dead Voices, typescripts, 1989
      - 13 February 1984-1990, typescripts, 1990
      - Tom, Dying of AIDS, typescripts, 1989
      - Unbeaten Play, typescripts and proofs, 1987 and undated, (2 folders)
      - Winter, manuscripts and typescript, 1961, 1989 and undated
      - Yom Kippur, typescript, 1988
      - Your Lies, typescript, undated
      - Table of Contents: typescript draft with corrections, undated
      - Printer's first proof, 1989
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1990, (2 folders)
      - Printer's proof, 1990 July
    - New Music: A Trilogy (plays, 1990) RESTRICTED (Box WP28)
      - August Snow
        - Handwritten notes and drafts, 1984-1985 and undated
        - First typescript draft with revisions, 1985 Jan.
        - Early typescript draft, 1985
        - Typescript draft, 1985
        - Bound copy, 1985
        - Rehearsal notes, 1985
        - Hendrix Players Production Program, 1985 Nov.
      - New Music
        - Handwritten fragment, 1985 Oct.
        - First draft, typescript, 1985 Oct.
        - Revised draft, typescript, 1985 Oct.
        - Typescript draft, 1985
        - Bound copy, 1985
      - Better Days, typescript draft, first revision, 1985 Dec.
      - Better Days, bound copy, 1985, (2 folders)
      - New Music, typescript draft, and related papers, 1987, undated (Box WP29)
      - August Snow, typescript draft, 1989 July
      - Night Dance, typescript draft, 1989 July
      - Better Days, typescript draft, 1989 July
      - Fragments, early drafts, 1989-1990 and undated
      - Reviews and articles, 1989
      - Miscellaneous related papers, 1989 Aug.-Oct. and undated
      - Copy of revised text as submitted for publication by Theater Communications Group, 1990, (2 folders)
    - The Foreseeable Future (stories, 1991) RESTRICTED (Box WP29)
      - The Fare to the Moon, early drafts, 1989
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, 1988 Feb.
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, 1988 Aug.
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, 1988 Sept. (Box WP30)
      - Setting copy with author's revisions, 1990 Aug., (2 folders)
      - Page proof, 1991, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Page Proof, 1991, (Folder 2 of 2)
      - Jacket Illustration, undated
    - Blue Calhoun (novel, 1992) RESTRICTED (Box WP30)
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, 1990, (2 folders)
      - Typescript draft with author's revisions, 1991 Jan., (4 folders) (Box WP31)
      - Notes, undated
      - Typescript draft, (4 folders)
      - Atheneum Ms., 1991, (3 folders) (Box WP32)
      - Original copyedited typescript, circa 1991, (4 folders)
      - Printer's Manuscript, circa 1991, (Folder 1 of 3) (Box WP33)
      - Printer's Manuscript, circa 1991, (Folders 2-3 of 3)
      - Revised Fragments, 1991
      - Proofreader's and master galleys, 1991, (2 folders)
      - Duplicate repro proofs, 1992, (6 folders)
      - Publisher's Prospectus 1992
      - Sample covers, undated
    - The Collected Stories (fiction, 1993) RESTRICTED (Box WP34)
      - The Company of the Dead, 1989
      - Deeds of Light, 1990
      - An Early Christmas, 1991, (2 folders)
      - The Enormous Door, undated
      - The Final News, 1990
      - The Golden Child, 1989
      - A Final Account, 1991
      - His Final Mother, 1990, (2 folders)
      - Home, 1990
      - Long Night, undated
      - A New Piece of Woods, 1988
      - Slow Night, 1990
      - This Wait, 1989
      - Watching Her Die, 1989
      - Typescript "as submitted to Atheneum" (photocopy), 1992, (Folders 1-3 of 5)
      - Typescript "as submitted to Atheneum" (photocopy), 1992, (Folders 4-5 of 5) (Box WP35)
      - Copyedited typescript (photocopy), circa 1992, (5 folders)
      - Master proof of front pages, preface, and author biography (photocopy), 1992 Nov. 30
      - Page proof with corrections (photocopy), 1992 Dec. 1, (Folder 1 of 4)
      - Page proof with corrections (photocopy), 1992 Dec. 1, (Folders 2-4 of 4) (Box WP36)
      - Second proofs of various stories' title pages (photocopies), 1992 Dec. 1
      - Sample pages, 1992
      - Page proof (photocopy), 1993 Jan. 19-20, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous drafts of front matter and jacket copy for various editions, 1992, 2003, and undated
      - Jacket proofs, 2003 and undated
    - A Whole New Life (nonfiction, 1994) RESTRICTED (Box WP37)
      - Typescript drafts, 1992-1993
        - With author's revisions, 1992 Sept. 18
        - With author's revisions, 1992 Oct. 2
        - Incomplete, circa 1992 Nov.
        - 1992 Dec. 1
        - 1993 Jan. 6
        - Circa 1993 Jan.-Apr., (2 folders)
        - With author's revisions, 1993 Apr. 9-17, (2 folders)
        - 1993 Apr. 27, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Typescript drafts, 1992-1993 (Box WP38)
        - 1993 Apr. 27, (Folder 2 of 2)
        - With notes by Alec Wilkinson, 1993 May 24-June, (2 folders)
        - With correspondence and notes by Daniel Voll, 1993 May 24-July, (2 folders)
        - Draft responding to Voll and Wilkinson, 1993 July 2, (2 folders)
        - With author's revisions, 1993 July 3-9, (2 folders)
        - 1993 July 22, (Folder 1 of 2)
      - Typescript drafts, 1992-1993 (Box WP39)
        - 1993 July 22, (Folder 2 of 2)
      - Proof with author's corrections, 1993 Oct. 6, (2 folders)
      - Draft of jacket copy, 1993 Nov. 16-1994 Jan. 14
      - Fragment of early draft, 1993
      - Repro (reproduction) proofs of several pages with author's corrections (photocopies), 1994 Jan. 11
      - Excerpt for Guideposts, 1994 Apr. 13
      - Jacket proof and specifications, 1999 Dec. 9-2000 Feb. 16
      - Sample pages for Scribner Classic Edition, 2000 Jan. 4
      - Draft of "possible new page 1," undated
      - Front cover copy, undated
      - Jacket proofs, undated
      - Typescript of audio abridgement by Lauren B. Church, undated, (2 folders)
    - The Promise of Rest (novel, 1995) RESTRICTED (Box WP40)
      - Notes, 1993 Nov.-Dec.
      - Typescript draft, 1994 Feb. 16, (3 folders)
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1994 Apr. 2-May 23, (3 folders)
      - Typescript draft, 1994 May 27, (3 folders)
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1994 June 2-29, (3 folders) (Box WP41)
      - Typescript draft, 1994 July 18, (4 folders)
      - Susan Moldow's questions on penultimate draft of 1994 August (Box WP42)
      - Original copyedited and corrected typescript, 1994 Oct., (4 folders)
      - Copyedited and corrected typescript (photocopy), 1994 Oct., (4 folders)
      - Revised design layouts and proposed jacket sketches, 1994 Oct. 25 (Box WP43)
      - Sample pages (three sets) 1994 Nov. 2-7
      - Script for audio abridgement, 1995 Feb. 28, (2 folders)
      - From the Author to the Trade, typescript, 1994 Oct. and undated
      - Drafts of jacket copy and quotes for various editions, 1994 Aug.-Nov. and undated
      - An Imminent Curse, typescript excerpt or early draft, undated
      - Ads, jacket proofs and specifications, undated
    - The Three Gospels (nonfiction, 1996) RESTRICTED (Box WP44)
      - The Good News According to John
        - Typescript with author's revisions, 1992 Nov. 7
        - Typescript fair copy, 1992 Nov. 10
        - Typescript with author's revisions, 1993 Jan. 8
        - Typescript with author's revisions (incomplete), 1994 Oct. 31-Nov. 7
      - An Apocryphal Gospel
        - Typescript with author's revisions, 1993 Mar. 20
        - Untitled typescript with author's revisions, 1993 July 7-10
      - Honest Accounts of a Memorable Life, (working title), typescript fair copy, 1994 Dec., (2 folders)
      - A Reckless Daring: the Gospel According to Mark, typescript and notes, 1994 Dec.
      - A New Thing Entirely: A Preface to the Good News According to Mark, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Jan. 25-28
      - A General Preface, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Jan. 28-29
      - A Modern Apocryphal Gospel: an Honest Account of a Memorable Life, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Jan. 30
      - The Strangest Story: the Good News According to John, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Feb. 3-10
      - According to Mark, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Mar. 24-29
      - According to John, typescript with author's revisions, 1995 Mar. 31-Apr. 5
      - Penultimate manuscript submitted to Susan Moldow, 1995 May 30, (3 folders) (Box WP45)
      - Notes on post-submission changes, 1995 June 29
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1995 Aug. 10-Oct. 5, (3 folders)
      - "Xerox of setting copy" (author's note), 1995 Oct., (3 folders)
      - Author's first proofs with corrections, 1995 Nov. 14, (2 folders) (Box WP46)
      - Proposed design and sample pages, 1995 Oct. 24
      - Author's suggestions for jacket copy, 1995 Aug.-Nov.
      - Samples of cover design, layout, and other illustrations, 1995-1996 and undated
      - Proposed jacket copy and blurbs for author's approval, 1996 Mar. 11
      - Complete draft typescript, fair copy, undated, (3 folders)
      - The Strangest Story, three typescript drafts, undated, (2 folders)
      - Becoming Contemporary With the Gospel Writers, printed material, undated
      - Flap copy, undated
      - Foreword, fragment, undated
      - Two fragments, typescript, undated
      - Cover proofs, undated
    - The Collected Poems (poetry, 1997) RESTRICTED (Box WP47)
      - An Actual Temple, typescripts with revisions, 1994 Jan. 8-10
      - The Closing, typescripts with revisions, 1996 Mar. 15-30
      - A Haven, typescripts, undated
      - A Long and Sizable Farewell, proof, 1996 Aug. 28
      - Three typescripts with author's revisions, 1996 Apr. 12-June 24, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence between author and Susan Moldow, with attachments of layouts of previous poetry collections and drafts of Preface, 1996 June 28-Aug. 1
      - Preface: five typescripts with author's revision, 1996 Aug. 7-12
      - Edited typescript (photocopy), 1996 Sept. 16, (2 folders)
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1996 Oct. 21, (Folder 1 of 3)
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1996 Oct. 21, (Folders 2-3 of 3 ) (Box WP48)
      - Copyedited typescript (photocopy), 1996 Oct. 21, (2 folders)
      - Master proof, 1996 Nov. 24, (3 folders)
      - Author's proof with queries answered, 1996 Nov. 24-1997 Jan. 7, (Folder 1 of 3 )
      - Author's proof with queries answered, 1996 Nov. 24-1997 Jan. 7, (Folders 2-3 of 3) (Box WP49)
      - The Unaccountable Worth of the World: two fair copy typescripts, circa 1997, (2 folders)
      - Untitled typescript, fair copy, undated
      - Jacket and ad proofs, 1996-1997 and undated
      - Ad copy, undated
      - The Laws of Ice photocopies, undated (originally published 1986), (2 folders)
      - The Use of Fire photocopies, undated (originally published 1986), (2 folders)
      - Vital Provisions photocopies, undated (originally published 1982)
    - Roxanna Slade (novel, 1998) RESTRICTED (Box WP50)
      - Typescript fragment with author's revisions, 1996 Feb. 5
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1996 Mar. 2
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1996 Mar. 20
      - Typescript--"A draft of Roxanna Slade," 1996 July 30
      - Typescript--"A draft of the first three parts of Roxanna Slade" (incomplete, missing pp. 69-171) 1996 Aug. 16, (2 folders)
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1996 Oct. 22-1997 Feb. 2, (4 folders)
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1997 Feb. 23-Apr. 2, (Folders 1-2 of 4)
      - Typescript with author's revisions, 1997 Feb. 23-Apr. 2, (Folders 3-4 of 4) (Box WP51)
      - Typescript, circa 1997 Apr.-June, (4 folders)
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1997 June 21-July 16, (Folders 1-3 of 4)
      - Original copyedited typescript, 1997 June 21-July 16, (Folder 4 of 4) (Box WP52)
      - Copyedited typescript (photocopy), 1997 June 21-July 16, (4 folders)
      - Master proof, 1997 Sept. 24, (2 folders)
      - Author's proof--first pass with author's corrections, 1997 Sept. 24-Oct. 14, (2 folders)
      - Proof--miscellaneous duplicate pages, 1997 Sept. 24 (Box WP53)
      - Author's proof, 1997 Dec. 16-1998 Jan. 4, (2 folders)
      - Typescript "as submitted to Scribner," 1998 June 24, (4 folders)
      - Preliminary jacket copies, 1997
      - Ad, 1998 May 11
      - Chronology for Roxanna Slade (two versions) and notes on second draft revisions, undated
      - Cover designs (ten samples), undated
      - Fragment--typescript page, undated
    - Learning a Trade (nonfiction, 1998) RESTRICTED (Box WP54)
      - Original notebooks, 1955-1997, (11 folders)
        Unbound manuscript and typescript pages that also contain some original drawings by the author and pasted-in clippings and photographs.
      - Notebooks (photocopy), 1955-1997, (Folders 1-3 of 6)
      - Notebooks (photocopy), 1955-1997, (Folders 4-6 of 6) (Box WP55)
      - Proof (photocopy), 1998 June 26, (6 folders)
      - Proof (photocopy, incomplete), undated, (5 folders) (Box WP56)
      - Preface: three typescript drafts, 1997 Sept. 29-Nov. 24
      - Footnotes: two typescript drafts, 1998 July 24-27
      - A Note on the Text, 1998 Aug. 15
      - Sample layouts, 1998 Feb. 24-Mar. 31
      - Jacket proof, undated
    - A Singular Family (novels, 1999) RESTRICTED (Box WP57)
      - Typescript, addition to preface, 1998 Aug. 9
      - Proofs and samples of back cover and interior design, 1998 Dec. 17-21
      - Page proof, 1998 Dec. 23-1999 Jan. 7, (4 folders)
      - Jacket proof, undated
    - Letter to a Man in the Fire (nonfiction, 1999) RESTRICTED (Box WP58)
      - Typescripts
        - With author's revisions, 1997 Oct. 29-Nov. 1, (2 folders)
        - Fair copy of 1997 Nov. 1 draft, undated
        - With author's revisions, 1997 Nov. 11, Nov. 19, Nov. 20, (3 folders)
        - With illustrations, 1997 Nov. 21
        - With author's revisions, 1997 Nov. 20
        - With Frank Lentricchia's notes, circa 1997 Dec.
        - With correspondence from author to Susan Moldow, 1998 Jan. 5
        - Draft of Further Reading, Listening, and Looking with author's revisions, 1998 Feb.
        - With queries from Susan Moldow, 1998 Mar. 4
        - With author's revisions, 1998 Apr. 5-8
        - With notes and queries by Eric Larson, 1998 Aug.
        - Copyedited original with author's corrections, 1998 Sept. 14-Oct. 21
        - Fair copy, 1998 Sept. 16
      - Proofs (three copies), 1998 Nov. 12, (3 folders) (Box WP59)
      - Proof with author's corrections (original and photocopy), 1998 Nov. 12-Dec. 29, (2 folders)
      - Second master proof, 1998 Dec. 30
      - Proof, 1999 Jan. 7
      - Master proof with author's corrections, 1999 Jan. 7
      - Proof with author's second pass changes, 1999 Jan. 7-13
      - Case specifications, 1998 Sept. 28-1999 Jan. 4
      - Jacket proofs, 2000 and undated
    - Feasting the Heart (nonfiction, 2000) RESTRICTED (Box WP60)
      Arranged chronologically within two groups: manuscripts and proofs created in preparing the published book, Feasting the Heart, and manuscripts for individual essays. Drafts of essays appear both as inline text within e-mail messages and as separate typescripts; for pieces published in the book, if there is a discrepancy between the working or broadcast title and the published title, the latter is used in labeling the folder.
      - Book publication materials
        - Original typescript (two photocopies, one with "as submitted" author's note), 2000, (2 folders)
        - Copyedited typescript with author's corrections (original and photocopy), 2000 Apr. 14, (2 folders)
        - Sample pages, 2000 May 22-24
        - Master proof, 2000 May 26, (2 folders)
        - Proof, 2000 May 26, (2 folders)
        - Proof with author's corrections, 2000 May 26-June 26, (Folder 1 of 2)
        - Proof with author's corrections, 2000 May 26-June 26, (Folder 2 of 2) (Box WP61)
        - Second master proof, 2000 June 28, (2 folders)
        - Second master proof (photocopy, incomplete), 2000 June 28
        - Second pass proofs with author's revisions, 2000 July 12, (2 folders)
        - Final proof, 2000 July 18, (2 folders)
        - Flap copy and comments by author, 2000 June-Oct.
        - Samples for various essays' title pages, 2000 July 13
        - Cover specifications and samples, 2000-2001
      - Individual essays
        - A Christmas in Rome, 1992 Nov. 13 and undated
        - Book Tour, 1995 June 19-30 and undated
        - The Last Great Weeper, 1995 Aug. 10
        - The Ghostwriter in the Cellar, 1995 Aug. 23-Sept.
        - Birthplace, 1995 Sept. 5
        - Oral History, 1995 Sept. 21
        - Wheelchair Travel, 1995 Oct. 20, 1996 July 13
        - E-mail containing drafts of various essays, 1995 Nov. 1-1996 Aug. 8 and undated
        - A Single Death Among Many, 1996 Feb. 21, July 27
        - My Tolerance Problem, 1996 June 29
        - The Mad Inventor, 1996 July 2
        - The Lucky Child's Christmas, 1996 Dec. 20
        - England in the Fifties, 1998 Sept. 24
        - Being Reviewed, undated